Guide to the Jack Lewis papers, 1915-2001.
Lewis, Jack papers,
- US Navy Documents
  - Subseries Iva. Alphabetical Correspondence Files
    - Correspondence O, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence P, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence Q, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence R, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence S, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence T, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence U-V, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence W, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence X-Y-Z, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Princeton correspondence and documents, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Letters from Navy pastors, 1945-1946 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Next-of-kin correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1938-1943 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence D-E-F, 1941-1942 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence G-H-I, 1938-1943 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence J-K-L, 1938-1943 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence Mc-M, 1940-1943 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence N-O, 1938-1943 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence P-Q-R, 1940-1943 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence S-T-U, 1940-1943 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence V-W-X-Y-Z, 1938-1943 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Official Navy correspondence, 1942-1949 (Box 26, Folder 46-54)
  - Subseries Vib. General Material
    - Follow-up file, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - T.P.C, 1940-1950 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      Includes aerial photographs of the proposed site of the new First Christian church.
    - Peace articles, 1940-1950 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Boot vespers, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Tech Presbyterian, 1941-09-1941-11 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Disbursing office, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 43)
      Includes SS Lew Wallace commendations, dinner program, rosters, and documents.
    - The Village Beecon, 1945-03-1945-05 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Recreation, 1940-1945 (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
      Includes clippings, comic strips, sports catalog, entertainment posters and programs, and program notes.
    - Christmas programs and pageants, 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Sunday school, Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Worship, 1941-1943 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Statements for courts: martials, 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Chaplain newsletters, 1940-1946 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Baptism notes, 1940-1945 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Chaplain reports, 1944-1946 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Church bulletins, 1945-1946 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Letters: Wash. and Dist., 1945 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Civilian funeral program, 1943-1948 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - 4th base, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Bulletins, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - US Naval Reserve material, 1965-1971 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Articles and correspondence concerning military years, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, questionnaires, certificates and promotion documents, 1946-1955 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Naval chapel specs/blueprints, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Navy regulations, music, etc, 1944-1950 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Navy documents: discharge, 1942-1950 (Box 26, Folder 41)
      Includes ID and certificates
    - Neptune certificate, 1942-1950 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Air Force certificate of appointment, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Navy commendation and letters of support/thanks, 1943-1950 (Box 26, Folder 44)
      Includes letter from Allan Shivers, Governor of Texas, and printed copy of Harry Truman letter
    - Navy publications/materials, 1942-1950 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Korean conflict recall, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Navy forms/bulletins, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - War Rations, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - War documents, 1942-1947 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - The History of the Chaplain Corps, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - They Answered the Call, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Jack Lewis' dog tags, 1942; MU-1864 (Box 48)
    - Jack Lewis' epaulettes, 1942; MU-1865 (Box 48)
    - Military pins, buttons, and insignia, Undated (Box 48)
    - USAT Lew Wallace Solemn Mysteries of the Ancient Order of the Deep initiation certificates, one is hand drawn, 1943 (Folder 1)
    - Large drafts of material for Dedication of Sugana Tareie and Dropican Memorial Chapel, 1943 (Folder 1)
  - Subseries Vic Funeral Services
    Each file contains information and letter on the deceased as well as a photograph of Lewis kneeling at the grave.
    - Bowers, Orville, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Brown, Dawson Daniel, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Buppert, Harry Jr., 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Campbell, Eugene Milton, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Carby, Henry Clayton Jr., 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Eastberg, Walter Herbert, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Edge, Kenneth Wallace, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Farmer, Jerry Dawson, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Gay, David Miles, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Glenn, Alton L., 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Harris, Benjamin Franklin, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Hesse, Harry Leonard, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Hickerson, Morris Livingston, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Hildebrant, Gilbert Shipley Jr., 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Holmes, Byron Joseph, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Holt, Curtis Eugene, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Ingram, Roy L., 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Jones, Lennie Charlie, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Kenney, James Joseph, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Keppelman, Thomas William, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Kielbik, William, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Lawrence, Russell Leroy, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Luskin, Weldon G., 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Malwitz, Edward Arthur, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Mitter, George Dewey Jr., 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Morken, Clarence Alfred, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Mowery, Linda, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Pritchett, John W., 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Ricks, James, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Riesz, Francis, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Rognrud, Gordon Everett, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Rybicki, Walter, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Shatwell, James Woodrow, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Strunk, Harry Daniel, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Switzer, William, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Takach, Rudolph, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Thomas, Frank L., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Traumann, Clemens Franz, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Vanover, Fred, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Watkins, Willie James, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Watson, Rube, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Watts, Richard Byrl, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Wheeler, Joseph E., 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Williams, Bernhart Arthur, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Williams, George Eugene, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Yewell, Malcolm Monnette, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - List of men aboard plane that crashed and requests for information, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Funeral documents, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Requests for next of kin, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 73)
- Series VII. Weddings (Restricted)
  - Wedding service documents, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Wedding service documents, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Wedding service documents, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Wedding service documents, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Wedding service documents, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Wedding service documents, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Wedding service documents, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Wedding service documents, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Wedding service documents, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Wedding service documents, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Wedding service documents, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Wedding service documents, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Wedding service documents, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Wedding service documents, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Wedding service documents, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Wedding service documents, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Wedding service documents, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Wedding service documents, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Wedding service documents, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Wedding service documents, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Wedding service documents, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Wedding service documents, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Wedding service documents, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Wedding service documents, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Wedding service documents, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Wedding service documents, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 9-10)
  - Wedding service documents, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 11-12)
  - Wedding service documents, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Wedding service documents, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Wedding service documents, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Wedding service documents, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Wedding service documents, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Wedding service documents, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Wedding service documents, 1997-2001 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Klempner/Siano wedding, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Rose/Cummings wedding, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Wedding service documents, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Wedding service materials: traditional and contemporary, Undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous wedding material, Undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Wedding cross-reference file, 1968-1981 (Box 19)
  - Sample wedding material, 1970-1980 (Box 20, Folder 1-4)
  - Contemporary wedding service, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Resource materials, 1960-1975 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Semi-traditional service, Undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Contemporary wedding service, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Marriage vows, Quaker excerpt, Undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Wedding future, 1970-1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Jewish, Christian, and Black ceremony, Undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Marriage, memorials, and funerals summary, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Other wedding services, 1987-1992 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous wedding and funerals, Undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Marriage ceremonies, Undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Series VIII. Funerals
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 17-18)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 22-23)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 24-25)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 9-10)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 12-13)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 15-16)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Funeral and memorial documents and correspondence, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Alumni memorial services, 1980-2002 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Memorial programs, 1990-2002 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Sample memorial services, 1983-2002 (Box 21, Folder 21-22)
  - Sample memorial services, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Bereavement group, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - AIDS: pems, writings, memorial services, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Obituaries and services, 1986-1999 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Memorial services: child, 1970-1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Special services: memorial, 1968-1980 (Box 22, Folder 6-7)
  - Special services: funerals, 1970-1976 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Pauline Allen, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Eric Frances Angiolillo-Bent, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Ethel Bailey, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Samantha Nichole Backers, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Nancy Bent, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Knight Biggerstaff, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Pamela Carson, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - James Colbert, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Alice Cook, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Anita Cummings, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Mildred Dent, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Alan Engelbrecht-Wiggans, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Henry Guerlac memorial, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Baxter Hathaway, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Evelyn Kalish, 2002-04 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Fred Marcham, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Georgia Tanner Moore, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Peter Olafson, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Robert Raymond memorial, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Lilly Reichman, Felix Reichman, 1987-1997 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Rothschild memorial, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Jason Seley, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Sienko, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Neal Stamp, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - John V. Stone, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Atsuki Watanabe, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - William Foote Whyte, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Anne Winter, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Dale Winter, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - George Winter, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Personal Documents
  - Subseries Ixa. Correspondence
    - Correspondence, 1947-1950 (Box 22, Folder 38-41)
      Includes two photographs and Western Clergy Fare certificate
    - Correspondence, 1950-1959 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1978-2002 (Box 22, Folder 43-44)
    - First Class Mail file, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
      Also includes study materials.
    - Mailers and correspondence from desk, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (work), 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Notes and correspondence from desk, 1980-1985 (Box 23, Folder 5-10)
    - Connie Goddard, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Letters and photographs, 1944-1951 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      Includes correspondence with Lyndon B. Johnson and University of Texas photographs
    - Personal correspondence, 1952-1958 (Box 23, Folder 16-17)
    - Jack's letter to Mary Durham on her 100th birthday, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Tuesday correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Thursday correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Fernando Llosa correspondence, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Harper and Row, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Nancy Gabriel, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence- B, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence- C-D, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence- F-G, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence- H-L, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence- M-P, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence- P-S, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence- S-Z, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1960-1975 (Box 42, Folder 1-16)
      Many letters include photographs of Lewis.
    - Correspondence and notes, 1976-1982 (Box 43, Folder 1-8)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1983-1990 (Box 44, Folder 1-10)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1990-1994 (Box 45, Folder 1-8)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1994-2001 (Box 46, Folder 1-11)
    - Correspondence and notes, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1980-1988 (Box 47, Folder 3-5)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1939-1955 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Alphabetical correspondence, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 2-9)
  - Subseries Ixb. General Materials
    - Birth certificates (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Personal papers and notes, 1951-1960 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Pamphlets and correspondence, 1970-1981 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Poetry, Undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Quotes and notes, 1983-1997 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - George's illness, orthomeolecular biology, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Contributors to help Jack and Mary get into Kendal, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Notes, pamphlets, correspondence, and four slides of unidentified people, 1950-1959 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Condolences on Jack Lewis' death, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Notes from unsorted files, 1973-1989 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Notes and brochures from unsorted files, 1965-1981 (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
    - Calendar/date books, 1950-1951 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Calendar/date books, 1952-1956 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Calendar/date books, 1962-1966 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Calendar/date books, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Calendar/date books, 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Calendar/date books, 1974-1976 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Calendar/date books, 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Calendar/date books, 1980-1983 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Calendar/date books, 1984-1987 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Calendar/date books, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Calendar/date books, 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Calendar/date books, 1995-1997 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Calendar/date books, 1998-2000 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Calendar/date books, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Calendar/date books, Undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Address books, Undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Identification cards, driving license, passports, 1944-1976 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Texas bank/mortgage, 1964-1970 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Keepsakes, 1999-2002 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      Contains some correspondence and photographs
    - Blueprint for addition to 704 Sparks and plot of whole hose and lot, 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Tejas Club anniversary packet, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Old papers: license and ordination, etc., 1940-1985 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Remembrances, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 44)
      Stories and notes about Jack Lewis
    - Mixed notes and correspondence from bag, 1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Church bulletins, 1950-1970 (Box 30, Folder 10-12)
      Many contain Lewis' annotations
    - Photographs and passports, 1950-2000 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Notes, 1940-1950 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Home maintenance, painting notes, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Notes and miscellany, 1968-1976 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Notes and miscellany, 1971-1990 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Documents and correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 30, Folder 27)
      Includes copies of will
    - Tejas Club, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Frank Rhodes/Kendal thanksgiving, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Alphabetical address files, Undated (Box 30, Folder 31-32)
    - Photo album of Lewis at work and performing ceremonies, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Copies of photographs of Jack and Mary Lewis, 1935-1937 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - 65th wedding anniversary photo, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Mounted photographs of scenery and people from John, 1971-1980 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Austin Presbyterian Theological Seminary appreciation certificate and miscellaneous documents, 1995-02-01 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - DeWitt Clinton Masonic Award photographs, invitations, notes, and correspondence, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Certificates and awards with supporting documents, 1961-2002 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - National Council of Alcoholism appointment certificate, Undated (Folder 1)
    - Black Gospel Festival award, 1996-02-18 (Box 51)
    - Community Service award, 1987-04-07 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Folder labelled "Family Photos", unidentified coupld, 1960-1980 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Chinese print on tissue paper, Undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Guest book, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Photo album of reception for Jack and Mary Lewis on their leaving UT for Scotland, 1950-04-13 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Calendar/date books, 1986-1991 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Ruth Pettengill Award, MU-1917 (Box 32)
      With letter and photograph from Jim Seward
    - Service award from Alcoholism Council of Tompkins County, 1976-01-29; MU-1918 (Box 32)
    - Service award from Alpha Phi Omega, 1981; MU-1919 (Box 32)
    - Distinguished community service award from Ithaca-Cayuga Rotary Club, 1987; MU-1920 (Box 32)
    - Desk name plate, Chaplain USNR, Undated; MU-1921 (Box 32)
    - Wood-mounted prayer, Undated; MU-1922 (Box 32)
    - Photographs, 1945-1960 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      Including Lewis receiving appointment as Chaplain, 1952.
    - Judgement at Nuremberg script, 1950-1965 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Prospectus for Provocation, TV Series, 1950-1965 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Plaster model of teeth, Undated (Box 48)
    - Clockface, for 13 years of service to CFLC, 1964-08 (Box 48)
    - Graduation cap, Undated (Box 48)
    - Pens and miscellaneous pins, Undated (Box 48)
    - Graduation hood, Undated (Box 48)
    - Lighters, Undated (Box 48)
    - Hourglass, Undated (Box 48)
    - Texas goodyear banner, Undated (Box 48)
    - Two flags, Undated (Box 48)
  - Subseries Xc. School years
    - Mid-syst. Theology paper, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - St. Andrews notebooks, 1950-1952 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - UT Austin records, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Class notes, 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Lay work centers, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Special papers, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Theology, 1938-1950 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Study abroad statement materials, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - St. Andrews calendar with photograph, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - St. Andrews University publications and pamphlets used by Lewis in class, 1948-1952 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Christian Ethics with Professor Forrester, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Old Testament ethics, Undated (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Class notebooks and notes, 1937- (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence and business matters concerned with passage, house, belongings, transport, etc., 1950-1951 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1947-1951 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Notebooks, St. Andrews handbook, 1950-1951 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Notebooks, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - St. Andrews brochures and travel guides, 1950-1951 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Mix of school notes and travel documents, 1947-1951 (Box 31, Folder 8-9)
      Removed from binder.
    - St. Andrews class photograph, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Schoolwork from binder, 1936-1952 (Box 39, Folder 9-11)
    - University of Texas senior yearbook, The Cactus, 1937 (Box 49)
    - University of Texas yearbook, The Cactus, 1936 (Box 51)
  - Subseries Xd. Travel
    - Jack Lewis goes abroad, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
      Documents and correspondence related to Lewis' time abroad.
    - Foreign currency, Undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Iona guides and pamphlets, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Iona community pamphlets and booklets, 1950-1958 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Family continental tour, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Correspondence, articles.
    - Trip information for Denmark, Germany, and Holland, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Travel correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 28, Folder 10)